Guide to the American Business Consultants, Inc. Counterattack: Research Files TAM 148
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series 99: Additional Miscellaneous Files
  - Duplicate Reports CI-CP (includes Henry Steel Commager, Committee for a Democratic Eastern Policy, Norman Corwin), 1947-1951 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Citizenship Clearing House, 1956-1959 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Duplicate Reports CQ-CZ, 1949-1953 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Duplicate Reports DA-DI (includes Vera Michells Dean and the Foreign Policy Association), 1949-1955 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Davis, Benjamin, 1962-1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Duplicate Reports DJ-DZ (includes James H. Durkin), 1949-1959 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Duplicate Reports EA-EL (includes Kermit Eby, Albert Einstein, Duke Ellington), 1948-1953 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Duplicate Reports EM-EZ (includes Haven Emerson, M.D.; Thomas Emerson, professor of law), 1949-1953 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Duplicate Reports FA-FH (includes Federation of Women Shareholders in American Business), 1949-1965 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Duplicate Reports FI-FP (includes Albert Fitzgerald), 1948-1953 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Duplicate Reports FQ-FZ (includes Clemens J. France; Irving S. Friedman; Stephen Frichtman, minister; Fulfillment Press, 1948-1953 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Duplicate Reports GA-GH (includes William Gailmor, Arthur Gaeth, John Garfield), 1948-1953 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Duplicate Reports GI-GP (includes Tom Glazer), 1949-1953 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Duplicate Reports GQ-GZ (includes Ernest A. Gross), 1950-1953 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Duplicate Reports HA-HAL (includes Gus Hall), 1949-1953 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Duplicate Reports HAM-HAZ (includes Hands Off China Rally, William H. Hastie, Clarence A. Hathaway, Elizabeth Hawes), 1948-1953 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Duplicate Reports HB-HH (includes Lillian Hellman, Donald Henderson), 1949-1954 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Duplicate Reports HI-HP (includes Paul G. Hoffman, Dr. John Haynes Holmes, Hotel and Restaurant Employees (AFL)), 1949-1955 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Duplicate Reports HQ-HZ, 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Duplicate Reports IA-IZ (includes International Workers' Order), 1949-1953 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Duplicate Reports JA-JH (includes Phillip J. Jaffee (J.W. Phillips), Jewish War Veterans), 1949-1955 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate Reports JI-JP (includes Matthew Josephson, author), 1951-1954 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Duplicate Reports JQ-JZ, 1938-1953 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Duplicate Reports KA-KH (includes David Karr, Danny Kaye, Rockwell Kent, Judge Dorothy Kenyon), 1948-1965 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Duplicate Reports KI-KP (includes Freda Kirchway, Hy Kraft), 1949-1953 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Duplicate Reports KQ-KZ, 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Duplicate Reports LA-LH (includes Burt Lancaster, Burton LeDoux, Sam Levenson, David Mortimer Livingston), 1946-1958 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Duplicate Reports LI-LP (includes Phillip Loeb, Edward H. Litchfield), 1949-1956 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Duplicate Reports LQ-LZ, 1948-1954 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Duplicate Reports MA (Archibald Macleish, professor from M.I.T.; Kirtley Mather, C. Henry Mather), 1948-1954 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Duplicate Reports Mc (includes Board of Education vs. Jerauld McGill, et. al.), 1948-1954 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Duplicate Reports ME-MH (includes Meat Cutters and Butchers of America (AFL), Ernest O. Melby), 1946-1953 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Duplicate Reports MI-MZ (includes Arthur Miller, A.F. Ashley Montagu), 1948-1953 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Duplicate Reports NA (includes The Nation; National Citizens Commission for Public Schools; National Council of the Arts, Sciences, and Professions; National Council of American-Soviet Friendship), 1947-1954 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Duplicate Reports (includes National Lawyers' Guild), 1946-1951 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Duplicate Reports NB-NZ, 1949-1955 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Duplicate Reports OA-OL (includes One World Award Committee), 1948-1953 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Duplicate Reports OM-OZ (includes Arthur Osman, Bishop G. Bromley Oxnam), 1948-1954 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate Reports PA-PH (includes Samuel J. Parks, "Peace Offensive," Gregory Peck, Institute of Applied Religion, Linus Pauling), 1947-1953 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Duplicate Reports PI-PP (includes Abraham Pomeranz; Adam Clayton Powell, Jr.), 1950-1960 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Duplicate Reports PQ-PZ (includes David Pressman, Pearl Primus), 1947-1953 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Duplicate Reports Q, 1953 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Duplicate Reports RA-RH (includes David Ramsey and Harold Faggen; William Redfield; Quentin Reynolds, editor and author), 1949-1955 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Duplicate Reports RI-RP (includes Wellington Roe, Franklin D. Roosevelt, Isadore Rosenberg), 1943-1953 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Duplicate Reports RQ-RZ (includes Jay Rubin; Ruder and Finn, Inc.; Russian War Relief, Inc), 1948-1953 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Duplicate Reports SA, 1949-1954 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Duplicate Reports SC (includes Frederick L. Schuman, professor; Marcel Scherer; Hubert Schon), 1948-1955 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Duplicate Reports SE-SH (includes Edwin Seaver; Vincent (James) Sheean, writer; Reverend Guy Emery Shipler, United Shoeworkers of America), 1949-1955 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Duplicate Reports SI-SL (includes Ellie Siegmeister, composer), 1949-1954 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Duplicate Reports SM-SS (includes Edgar Snow, Roy Soden, "Spotlight on Asia Dinner"(Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy), 1949-1960 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Duplicate Reports ST-SZ, 1949-1964 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Duplicate Reports TA-TZ (includes R.J. Thomas, Jeanette Turner, Martin K. Tytell), 1949-1958 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Duplicate Reports UA-UZ (includes United Productions of America, United World Federalists, Louis Untermeyer, Harold Urey), 1948-1954 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Duplicate Reports VA-VZ (includes Elkan Valden), 1949-1953 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Duplicate Reports WA-WH (includes J. Raymond Walsh, Colston E. Warne), 1948-1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Duplicate Reports WI-WZ (includes World Youth and Student Festival), 1949-1953 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Duplicate Reports Y-Z (includes Yale University, Coleman Young, Youth of all Nations), 1948-1953 (Box 44, Folder 6)